Okay, how about this?
Nobody gets to be the Flash.
(Leonard:)We all change. Agreed?
ALL:
Agreed.
(Leonard:)I call Frodo!
ALL:
Damn.
(Penny(arriving):)Hey.
(Raj(Entering dressed as Thor):)Sorry I'm late, but my hammer got stuck
in the door on the bus.
- You went with Thor?
- What?
(Raj:)Just because I'm Indian,
I can't be a Norse god?
(Raj:)No, no, no, Raj has to be an Indian god.
(Raj:)That's racism.
(Raj:)I mean, look at Wolowitz. He's not English,
but he's dressed like Peter Pan.
Sheldon is neither sound nor light,
but he's obviously the Doppler effect.
- I'm not Peter Pan, I'm Robin Hood.
- Really?
(Raj:)Because I saw Peter Pan
and you're dressed exactly like Cathy Rigby.
(Raj:)She was a little bigger than you,
but it's basically the same look, man.